AMNISH LOHIRE

Audio Engineer

Contact

Address

Mumbai, India, 421501

Phone

(+91)9920191600

E-mail

amnish.lohire@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com /in/amnish-lohire-233a6255

Skills

-GOOD KNOWLEDGE OF ACOUSTICS, SYSTEM SET UP ENGINEERING AND CREW MANAGEMENT

KNOWLEDGE AND
EXPERIENCE OF WORKING
UNDER ALL SITUATIONS AND
WITH ALL PROFESSIONAL
EQUIPMENTS,

IMMENSE EXPERIENCE IN WORKING FOR DESTINATION WEDDING EVENTS

ALWAYS SUPPORTIVE OF TEAM WORK

PHYSICALLY FIT AND WILLING
TO WORK AND TRAVEL
WHEN SITUATION DEMANDS

A Professional Live Sound Engineer with experience of over 12 yrs in handling LIVE SOUND events, concerts, broadcast events, television shows, conferences, musical plays, religious events, etc..... ABILITY AND EXPERIENCE of mixing both FOH and Monitor for all genres of artists..... having experience and knowledge of studio mixing, mastering, recording of all work profile.... A musician with good knowledge of musical instruments and music production.... dedicated and always motivated to work since LIVE SOUND is my passion and interest.

Knowledge in system designing of all major speaker brands(JBL,D&B,MAYER SOUND,L'ACOUSTICS ETC)
Ability in handling all major brand digital and analog consoles(AVID,DIGICO,SOUNDCRAFT,ALLEN & HEATH,ETC)
Well informed and updated with latest technology in professional live sound
ability in handling all major recording softwares

Work History

INTERNATIONAL PROJECTS

VARIOUS ARTISTS AND COMPANIES

Mixing And System Duties For Akon Show ,Mixing And System Duties For Alexandra Stan Show ,Mixing And Sytem Duties For Shaggy Show ,Monitoring Mixing For Akon ,Monitor Mix Duties For Osibisa,Foh Duties For Jason Samuel Smith,Chitresh Das And Antonia Hidalgo India Tour,Mixing And System Dities For Guthrie Govan India Tour Mumbai Show,Mixing And System Duties For Ink Conference 2012 Performing Artists,Foh And Monitor Mixing Trilok Gurtu Tour India,Foh And System Duties For Sunburn Music Festival Stage

2015-03 -Current

Freelance Live Sound Engineer

Self

Working As Mix Engineer For Various Artists &Bands(Abhijeet Sawant,Khushboo Grewal,Astha Gill,Shraddha Sharma,Mansheel Gujral,Desi Swag).

Foh And System Engineer For Various Music Festivals, Launch Events, Conferences And Entertainment Events.

MORE THAN 12 YRS OF WORK EXPERIENCE IN PROFESSIONAL LIVE SOUND Foh And System Engineer For Various Theatre
Performances And Plays...(Foh And System Engineer For
Famous Sound Of Music Play In Mumbai)
Involved In System Designing And Upgradation Of
System With Different Sound Companies.

2013-07 - SENIOR SOUND ENGINEER

2015-03 E2TECH, MUMBAI, MAHARASHTRA

Handling Foh And System Designing For Events, System Up Gradation And Monitoring Maintainance Of Equipments.

2010-10 - FREELANCE SOUND ENGINEER

2013-07 SELF

Worked As Freelance Engineer For All Reputed Companies In India Handling Events And Designing System For Events.

2008-05 - SENIOR SOUND ENGINEER

2010-09 RICH AUDIO, MUMBAI, INDIA

Responsible For Managing All Technical And Foh Duties Involved In An Event And As Well As Maintainance Of Equipments

Involved In Installation Of Sound At Various Religious

Places, Clubs, Auditorium

SCHOOLS,ETC For Managing All Technical And Foh

Duties Involved In An Event And As Well As

Maintainance Of Equipments

INVOLVED IN INSTALLATION OF SOUND AT VARIOUS

RELIGIOUS PLACES, CLUBS, AUDITORIUM

INVOLVED IN INSTALLATION OF SOUND AT VARIOUS

RELIGIOUS PLACES, CLUBS, A

2007-08 - **SOUND ENGINEER**

2008-04 SOUND.COM, MUMBAI, INDIA

Worked With One Of The Leading Sound Company In India....Worked On Almost All Prestigious Events In India....Worked On Major International Acts, Festivals

Education

2006-10 - **SOUND ENGINEERING AND RECORDING**

2007-05	ARTS
	DIGITAL FILM SCHOOL MUMBAI - MUMBAI
2000-06 -	GRADUATE: COMMERCE

Interests

Composing Music, Playing Guitar, Bikes And Pets